[
    {
        "question": "What does SQL stand for?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Structured Question Language",
            "Sequential Query Logic",
            "Simple Query Language"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Structured Query Language"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which command is used to create a new database in MySQL?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "MAKE DATABASE dbname;",
            "ADD DATABASE dbname;",
            "NEW DATABASE dbname;"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "CREATE DATABASE dbname;"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which MySQL command is used to select data from a database?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "EXTRACT",
            "SHOW",
            "GET"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "SELECT"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which SQL clause is used to filter the results?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "SORT BY",
            "FILTER",
            "ORDER BY"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "WHERE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which SQL keyword is used to sort the result-set?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "SORT",
            "FILTER BY",
            "RANK BY"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "ORDER BY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default port number of MySQL?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1521",
            "27017",
            "1433"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3306"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which function is used to return the number of rows in MySQL?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "SUM()",
            "MAX()",
            "TOTAL()"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "COUNT()"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which JOIN returns all rows when there is a match in one of the tables?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "INNER JOIN",
            "LEFT JOIN",
            "RIGHT JOIN"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "FULL OUTER JOIN"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which MySQL statement is used to add a new row of data?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "APPEND INTO",
            "INSERT NEW",
            "ADD ROW"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "INSERT INTO"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement is used to remove a table and all its data in MySQL?",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "REMOVE TABLE table_name;",
            "DELETE table_name;",
            "CLEAR TABLE table_name;"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DROP TABLE table_name;"
    }
]
